Her dreams are about to get a whole lot bigger
Phat Girlz is a comedy, romance film directed by Nnegest Likké.
Two large women struggle to find love and
acceptance in a culture where thin is in.
Their lives take a dramatic turn when they meet the men of
their dreams in completely unexpected ways.
Jazmin Biltmore, played by Mo'Nique.
Dr. Tunde Jonathan, played by Jimmy Jean-Louis.
Akibo, played by Godfrey.
Stacey, played by Kendra C. Johnson.
Mia, played by Joyful Drake.
Robert Myer, played by Eric Roberts.
Phat Girlz is a 2006 American romantic comedy film written and directed by
Nnegest Likké and starring Mo'Nique, as well as Kendra C.
Johnson, Jimmy Jean-Louis, Godfrey, and Joyful Drake.
The film explores themes of overweight woman, self
esteem, body image, woman director, plus size.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.